Lesson 71  He's awful!
他讨厌透了!
What's Ron Marston like, Pauline?
Pauline,Ron Marston是怎样一个人?
He's awful!
他讨厌透了!
He telephoned me four times yesterday,
他昨天给我打了4次电话,
He telephoned the office yesterday morning
他昨天上午和下午
and yesterday afternoon.
把电话打到了我的办公室,
My boss answered the telephone.
是我的老板接的.
What did your boss say to him?
你老板是怎么对他说的?
He said, 'Pauline is typing letters.
他说：“Pauline正在打信,
She can't speak to you now!'
她现在不能同你讲话!”
Then I arrived home at six o'clock yesterday evening.
后来,我昨晚6点钟回到家里.
He telephoned again.
他又打来电话,
But I didn't answer the phone!
但我没接.
Did he telephone again last night?
他昨天夜里又打电话了吗?
Yes, he did.
是的,打了.
He telephoned at nine o'clock.
他在9点钟又打来了电话.
What did you say to him?
你对他怎么说的?
I said, 'This is Pauline's mother.
我说：“我是Pauline的母亲.
Please don't telephone my daughter again!'
请不要再给我女儿打电话了!”
Did he telephone again?
他又打了没有?
No, he didn't!
没有!